Too much ... for one movie!
Supervixens is a comedy film directed by Russ Meyer.
Clint must flee after his wife is killed by a psychopathic
cop, who tries to pin the murder on him.
Super Angel / Super Vixen / Wife, played by Shari Eubank.
Clint Ramsey, played by Charles Pitts.
Harry Sledge, played by Charles Napier.
SuperSoul / Telephone Operator, played by Uschi Digard.
Super Lorna, played by Christy Hartburg.
Super Cherry, played by Colleen Brennan.
Supervixens is a 1975 American film directed by American filmmaker Russ Meyer.
The cast features Meyer regulars Charles Napier, Uschi Digard, and Haji.
The film also features Shari Eubank (in a dual role) in one of her only
two film roles and Christy Hartburg in her only film role.
The film explores themes of psychopath, eroticism,
impotence, dark comedy, false accusations.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.